Harold Bauer Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Realia (Box 13-14)
  - Medal, boxed, inscribed "Por Isabel la Católica" (Madrid, Spain). (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Medal, boxed, inscribed "Honneur et Patrie" (Paris, France). (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Medal, bronze, 2 5/8" (6.8 cm) diameter, without inscription. (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Medal, bronze, 3 1/8" (8 cm) diameter, from the society "La Trompette," inscribed "Souvenir de E. Lemoine/Harold Bauer." (Box-folder 14/6)